<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Recipes</string>
    <string name="tikka_masala_recipe">Add your chicken thighs to a large bowl. Add in your vegetable oil, yogurt, lemon juice, garlic, seasonings, and ginger. Mix until fully combined. Cover and refrigerate for a minimum 1 hour, but preferably overnight.
In a large pan, heat 1-2 tbsp ghee (or vegetable oil) over medium/high heat. Cook your chicken about 80% of the way through, or until you see some browning happen on the bottom of the pan. Remove from the pan and set aside.
Reduce heat to medium/low, and add in another touch of ghee. Add in your onion, optional green chili, and a pinch of salt. Saute for a few minutes, scraping the brown bits off the bottom of the pan. Pour in your seasonings and toast for a couple of minutes.
Add in your garlic and grated ginger, stir to combine. Let cook for 30 seconds.
Clear a center in the middle of your pan and add in your tomato paste. Let it cook off in the pan for a minute or so before incorporating with the rest. Then stir to combine.
Pour in your tomato sauce, ⅓ cup water, and a pinch of salt. Stir and simmer on low for 30 min.
While your sauce is simmering, prepare your rice. Boil two cups of water with 1-2 tsp of ghee. Once boiling, pour in two cups of Minute Instant Basmati Rice, stir, cover, and remove from heat. Let sit for 5-7 minutes, or until the water has evaporated. Fluff and set aside (keep warm).
Once your sauce is finished simmering, pour in your cream and a pinch of salt. Stir to combine. If your sauce seems too thick, add in a few splashes of water at a time until you reach your desired consistency. You can also blend the sauce at this step before adding your chicken.
Add back in your chicken and the juices. Stir and simmer for another 5-10 minutes.
Garnish with a drizzle of cream and a sprinkle of cilantro. Serve with your basmati rice and fresh naan. Enjoy!</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to My\u00A0Recipes!</string>
    <string name="create_acc">Create account</string>
    <string name="remind_password">Remind password</string>
    <string name="WEB_CLIENT_ID">466024413319-1aovp1cac84bpdb3a01jut9rqo3as4mf.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="or"><u>or</u></string>
</resources>